Viewers, the message about Africa: No African country can succeed alone.
African countries need each other to succeed.
Dear Africa, we should not let other fellow Africans feel unwelcome to our countries.
Africa unite!
Let us pray viewers all over the world.
Stretch your hand towards the screen.
Wherever you are under the influence of my voice -
right now, I say to that infirmity, I say to that sickness:
let the power of God come down!
Wherever the disease is located - in your blood, tendons, fluids and bones -
whatever name they call it - kidney problem - out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
I command them out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Whatever situation you are in right now, with God all things are possible.
Never a sickness, never a burden Jesus cannot solve.
I command that situation - be surmounted, in the name of Jesus!
Be moved, in the name of Jesus! I command them out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
I say - out, in the name of Jesus!
That situation in your blood, fluids, tendons, kidney - whatever name they call it -
never a sickness Jesus cannot heal; never a disease Jesus cannot cure.
Be cured, in the name of Jesus!
Be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Right now, let your story change!
I'm healed, I'm delivered, I'm saved!
Let your story change! Yes, let your story change, in the name of Jesus Christ!
With God, all things are possible -
just believe.
With God, all things are possible.
I say to your business - flourish, in the name of Jesus!
I say to your career - be restored, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever stage your career is - great, right now!
Great!
This is the voice of God.
I say to your career, whatever stage your career is - imbalanced, epileptic -
your business, your finances - I say, great, great, move, in the name of Jesus!
Move, in the name of Jesus!
Dry bones shall rise again!
Your family, your marriage - be restored, in the name of Jesus!
I say to you, anywhere you are, whatever medium you are using to view us right now -
right now, just believe, in the name of Jesus, by faith -
you are healed, delivered and set free, in the name of Jesus!
I can't wait to hear your testimony!
Once again, Africa, Africa, Africa!
Africa has neglected her youth.
Africa has abandoned the youth to themselves.
Africa has failed to provide provision for her youth.
Anytime I think about the future of Africa, I have sleepless nights.
Everything looks gloomy, sunless, dark, darksome, shadowy and dull.
Africa, Africa!
Lord Jesus, we commit the nations of Africa into Your hands - redeem the nations,
redeem the continent of Africa, in the name of Jesus!
Redeem our leaders, in the name of Jesus!
Wherever there are troubled spots all over the world,
Father, Lord Jesus, come and rescue the nations.
All over the world, rescue the nations. There is trouble all over the world.
Father, we know with You, all things are possible.
We know with You, dry bones shall rise again.
Whatever pain, whatever area - the nations that are at war,
Father, Lord Jesus - be calm, let peace restore - unity!
I can hear breakthrough, in the name of Jesus.
Thank You, Lord!
I leave you in faith.
You will see me back in faith.
I shall meet you in faith. Thank you.